{
    "subject": "resource/North_Korea",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Pyongyang",
    "human_readable": "The capital of North Korea is Pyongyang.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8799456357955933,
            "question": "Which country has Pyongyang as its capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7965698838233948,
            "question": "When was Pyongyang established as the capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7816640734672546,
            "question": "What is the capital of North Korea?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5918425917625427,
            "question": "Where is Pyongyang located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5822689533233643,
            "question": "Is Pyongyang a major city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44808265566825867,
            "question": "What are some notable landmarks in Pyongyang?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35913315415382385,
            "question": "What is the population of Pyongyang?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3294374346733093,
            "question": "What are some important cultural events that take place in Pyongyang?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2606409192085266,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Pyongyang?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15679478645324707,
            "question": "What language is spoken in Pyongyang?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of North Korea is Pyongyang.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8881_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Pyongyang?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8881_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some important cultural events that take place in Pyongyang?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8881_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Pyongyang?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8881_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8881_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8881_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8881_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8881_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8881_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8881_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8881_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8881_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8881_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8881_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided supports the triple, as multiple documents mention that Pyongyang is indeed the capital of North Korea."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Pyongyang is the capital city of North Korea, thus supporting the statement \"The capital of North Korea is Pyongyang.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}